MOHIT SETHI

PROFILE

I am a dedicated and self-taught game programmer. I have worked on published games, one of which has more than ten million installs on Google Play Store; furthermore, I have even published my games. My main goal is to keep advancing my knowledge and learning. Some of my hobbies include tinkering with computers, gaming, and obsessing over One Direction songs.

LINKS & CONTACTS

- in linkedin.com/in/mohitsethi
- github.com/mohitsethi99
- (+91) 9650814836
- gamedevmohit@gmail.com
- M32 NIT-5 Faridabad, Haryana, IN

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Experience in the following programming languages : C#, C++, C, JAVA, JAVASCRIPT.
- Experience in the following Design or Development tools: Unity 3D, Unreal Engine 4, Cocos Creator, Android Studio.
- Knowledge of the following programming languages: GLSL, Python, Shell, HTML, CSS.
- Fluent in English and Hindi.

EXPERIENCE

Game Developer Intern

Udayy - May 2020 - Present

As a game developer at Udayy which is an Ed. Tech firm, my responsibilities include developing games end to end for kids to learn Maths and English, along with the incorporation of math logic into the games. Check out more at https://www.udayy.com/.

Indie Game Developer

WolfHash Studios Nov 2018 - Present

As a co-founder and a solo game programmer, I was solely responsible for the entire development pipeline. Our product (Shootzy) is a top-down game that was made and published in 25 days using Unity 3D, and extensive use of its Lightweight Render Pipeline.

Game Developer Intern

Moong Labs Technologies Pvt Ltd - Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

I was responsible for camera and replay camera movement, bowling AI and pitch distribution for their <u>cricket game</u> made with Unity3D and C# published under Nazara Games that has over ten million installs and over two hundred thousand monthly active users.

Intern App Developer

Aravali College of Engineering & Management - Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

I was the sole developer responsible for Aravali College of Engineering & Management, which is a student-college update app made with Android Studio and Java. My responsibilities included the initial research, planning and managing the project, designing the features, and writing out the specs.

Volunteer Experience: Unity Instructor

Aravali College of Engineering & Management - May 2016 - June 2018

I ran workshops to teach game development at Aravali College of Engineering and Management that included a game source - Cut the cord, that I developed alongside my academic studies. My motto is to spread awareness about the game industry, specifically about the Unity Game Engine with the basics of C#. It helped me a lot in improving my presentation skills, Unity 3D, and C# knowledge.

EDUCATION

- JC Bose University Of Science And Technology BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science 2017 - 2021
- St. Joseph's Convent School High School, Secondary School 2005 - 2017